# JAG SINGH

(206) 304-3009 | jagrajs@icloud.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | jag.ai

## **ABOUT**

Experienced retail sales professional transitioning into data science and artificial intelligence.

Currently pursuing an analyst role where I can apply my educational experience and analytical skills to be a great asset to your company.

Utilizing various online resources to expand skills in computer science and advanced mathematics to meet market demand.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Product Advisor May 2018 - Present

Microsoft | Bellevue, WA

- Demonstrate and sell Microsoft products and services to help customers achieve more.
- Generate business leads to increase store revenue.
- Diagnose, troubleshoot, and resolve common technical issues.
- Deliver workshops and personal trainings to educate and inspire clients.

Sales Associate August 2012 - May 2018

Nordstrom | Tukwila, WA

- Created a positive customer experience and delivered stellar customer service.
- Increased average customer transaction value by opening Nordstrom Rewards accounts.
- Analyzed real time sales data to focus resources and optimize sales.
- Deliver workshops and personal trainings to educate and inspire clients.

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Arts in Communication** | University of Washington

2014 - 2017

• Coursework included advanced public speaking and a concentration in mathematics.

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Python (2 years), SQL (1 year)

Tools: NumPy, SymPy, SciPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, MATLAB, Octave

Markup & Web: LaTeX, HTML, CSS

Productivity: Microsoft Office 365 (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, OneNote, Outlook)

**Languages**: English (fluent), Punjabi (working proficiency)

,